<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hacktoberfest | Golemverse</title>
    <link>/categories/hacktoberfest/</link>
      <atom:link href="/categories/hacktoberfest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>hacktoberfest</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© ThinkR - 2021</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/golemverse_banner.png</url>
      <title>hacktoberfest</title>
      <link>/categories/hacktoberfest/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join HacktoberFest 2021 with {golem}!</title>
      <link>/post/golem-hacktoberfest-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/golem-hacktoberfest-2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us for &lt;a href=&#34;https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/&#34;&gt;Hacktoberfest 2021&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;code&gt;{golem}&lt;/code&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hacktoberfest is an online event, happening all over the world, where everyone is invited to open a pull request on a repo that has issues labelled &lt;code&gt;hacktoberfest&lt;/code&gt;.
The idea of this event is to gather developers (newbies or seasoned), and make them work together on open source projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this second year, I&#39;m happy to invite developers from the R community to take part to Hacktoberfest with &lt;code&gt;{golem}&lt;/code&gt;.
I&#39;ve started to label some issues inside the repository with the &lt;code&gt;hacktoberfest&lt;/code&gt; label, so that you can join the party, starting tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every time you&#39;ll open an issue with this label, you&#39;ll also find two other labels: the difficulty level (novice, intermediate, advanced), and a time estimate (low, medium, high).
This will help you evaluate if you can try and tackle this issue or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&#39;ll find them all on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ThinkR-open/golem/issues?q=is%3Aissue+is%3Aopen+sort%3Aupdated-desc+label%3Ahacktoberfest&#34;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;.
Feel free to leave a comment on the issue you&#39;d like to tackle, and of course to ask questions if the issue is not detailled enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m planning on release a minor version of &lt;code&gt;{golem}&lt;/code&gt; (0.3.1) at the end of this month, with all the new features and bug fixes that we will all have worked on during the month 🤘&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you on GitHub!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
